Guide to the Stephen Harmon Photographs 1942, 1968-2017 PR 362
New-York Historical Society
- Series D.III. New York City Buildings, Parks and Other Cityscapes (2002 and later), 2002-2017; 426.4 Megabytes (1571 digital images in JPG format)
  The series holds photos of various areas of the city, primarily in Manhattan but also of Brooklyn, Queens and the Bronx. Within Manhattan, areas that figure prominently include Central Park, the Upper West Side, 125th Street, Midtown, Greenwich Village, and Chinatown. The views are primarily exteriors of buildings, storefronts, parks, street views, and street traffic. These views range from close details, such as signage, shop displays, and doorways, to broad vistas of the skyline as seen down avenues, across the East River, or from bridges. Interior views of buildings are much less common in the series and their occurrence are typically noted in the container list. The specific scope of the series and the determination of which photos to include in it was made by the processing archivist.
  - Lower Manhattan skyline and Brooklyn Bridge, from FDR Drive (1 photo + 1 email), 2002 February (Digital folder 20171024, Digital file 2_1, email)
  - Coney Island building at Surf and 12th Street, closed for winter (1 photo + 1 email), 2002 February (Digital folder 20171018, Digital file 4_1, email)
  - Firehouse. Fire Patrol 2 (1 photo + 1 email), 2005 November 15 (Digital folder 20170509, Digital file 4_1, email)
  - SoHo. West Broadway at Spring Street (1 photo + 1 email), 2005 November (Digital folder 20170509, Digital file 3_1, email)
  - Greenwich Village. Cafe del Mar at Bleecker & MacDougal, 2005 November (Digital folder 20170822, Digital file 2_1, email)
  - SoHo building with fire escapes (1 photo + 1 email), circa 2005 (Digital folder 20170816, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Arthur Avenue, Bronx's "Little Italy" (9 photos), 2006 January 26 (Digital folder 20130130, Digital file 1_1-9)
  - Upper Manhattan. 125th Street (3 photos + 2 emails), circa January 2006 (Digital folder 20170509, Digital file 1_1-3, 2 emails)
    2 photos in the vicinity of 125th and Malcolm X Boulevard, and one of Frank's Papaya at Lexington Avenue.
  - Greenpoint. God Bless Deli (1 photo + 1 email), 2006 January (Digital folder 20170328, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Williamsburg, Corner Bakery, Division Avenue & Roebling Street (1 photo + 1 email), 2006 January (Digital folder 20170511, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Central Park South skyline (1 photo + 1 email), 2006 July (Digital folder 20170512, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Firehouse. (1 photo + 1 email), 2006 July (Digital folder 20170512, Digital file 3_1, email)
    Engraved in frame of truck bay: H&L Co. 3, Water Tower No. 2; painted on door of truck bay: 3 Truck, Battalion 6.
  - Central Park. Sheep Meadow (1 photo + 1 email), 2006 September (Digital folder 20170925, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Various (7 photos + 7 emails), 2006 October (Digital folder 20170514, Digital file 2_1-7, 7 emails)
    Includes: 1) Upper West Side: Ansonia (November); 2) Metropolitan Museum of Art, front steps; 3) 14th Street subway entrance; 4) Greenwich Village laundromat; 5) Carousel in Central Park; 6) East Village: Urban Vets. Animal Hospital, mural; 7) Katz's Delicatessen.
  - Various (11 photos + 6 emails), 2006 (Digital folder 20170513, Digital file 1_01-11, 6 emails)
    Includes: 1) Upper West Side: taxis on Broadway at about 70th Street (April); 2) SoHo: Deli on corner of Spring and Green Streets; 3) Lower Manhattan: Lafayette Street looking south; 4) Door of a taxi with fare rates; 5) SoHo: Tenement building with fire escapes at Kenmare Street near Lafayette; 6&7) Chinatown; 8&9) Chinatown: bakery neon signage (2006 or 2007); 10) top of Woolworth Building (2006 or 2007); 11) SoHo: Subway entrance at Spring and Lafayette streets. All November unless noted.
  - Red Hook, Brooklyn. Wolcott Street, Le Comte & Co. building (1 photo + 1 email), 2007 February (Digital folder 20170518, Digital file 3_1, email)
  - Central Park South, looking west to the Time Warner Center (1 photo + 1 email), 2007 April (Digital folder 20170520, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Chelsea. 24th or 26th street (1 photo + 1 email), 2007 April (Digital folder 20170521, Digital file 2_1, email)
  - Greenwich Village. MacDougal Street Ale House (1 photo + 1 email), 2007 April (Digital folder 20170523, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Coney Island (12 photos + 1 email), 2007 August (Digital folder 20170818, Digital file 2_01-12, email)
    Boardwalk stores and stands, "Freak Show" and other signages, Cyclone, Wonder Wheel.
  - Midtown. Rowhouses on West 57th Street at 10th Avenue (2 photos + 1 email), 2007 September (Digital folder 20170927, Digital file 1_1-2, email)
  - Views from New York Harbor (3 photos + 2 emails), 2007 September (Digital folder 20170927, Digital file 2_1-3, 2 emails)
    Two images of the southern tip of Manhattan and one of the Verrazzano Narrows Bridge.
  - Views from the Chrysler Building's 61st floor (46 photos + 5 emails), 2008 February (Digital folder 20170711, Digital file 1_01-46, 5 emails)
    Images made one evening and the following morning, after an overnight snowfall. Several images emphasize the eagles (2 with snow). Others are views to the east toward Brooklyn and Queens, west toward New Jersey, and south through Midtown and into lower Manhattan. Includes both broad views of skylines and detailed views of rooftops and specific structures (United Nations, MetLife Building, Empire State Building, Edward Koch Queensboro Bridge/59th Street Bridge).
  - Upper West Side. Hotel Empire at Broadway and 66th Street (1 photo + 1 email), 2008 March (Digital folder 20170526, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Canal Street and Chinatown (26 photos + 4 emails), 2008 April (Digital folder 20170606, Digital file 1_01-26, 4 emails)
    8 views on Canal and 10 in Chinatown of pedestrians, storefronts, signage, vendors. Some images seem to be duplicates, having been donated in both 2013 and 2017.
  - Midtown. Larry Flynt's Hustler Club (1 photo + 1 email), 2008 May (Digital folder 20170821, Digital file 1_1, email)
    12th Avenue at 51st Street
  - Various (3 photos + 1 email), 2008 August (Digital folder 20170608, Digital file 1_1-3, email)
    1) Midtown: 6th Avenue looking north from 45th Street; 2) Skyline view of Lower Manhattan's east side, taken from a water taxi on the East River south of the Brooklyn Bridge; 3) New York Water Taxi ferry boat on the East River with Brooklyn and Manhattan bridges in background.
  - Bronx (1 photo + 1 email), 2008 September (Digital folder 20170609, Digital file 2_1, email)
    View from Joyce Kilmer Park across Walton Avenue to storefronts and glimpse of Yankee Stadium in background.
  - Guggenheim Museum, view from 5th Avenue at 88th Street (1 photo + 1 email), 2008 September (Digital folder 20170616, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Chinatown morning (37 photos), 2008 October (Digital folder 20130126, Digital file 1_01-37)
    Many of these images are of people practicing tai chi on a neighborhood basketball court.
  - View to the outside from within the street level dining area in Alice Tully Hall at Lincoln Center (1 photo + 1 email), 2009 June (Digital folder 20170605, Digital file 2_1, email)
  - Chinatown (14 photos), 2010 April (Digital folder 20130125, Digital file 1_01-14)
  - Empire State Building framed in an arch of the Manhattan Bridge (1 photo + 1 email), 2010 April (Digital folder 20170621, Digital file 5_1, email)
  - SoHo. Building fire escape (1 photo + 1email), 2011 January (Digital folder 20170621, Digital file 4_1, email)
  - Various (7 photos + 5 emails), 2011 April (Digital folder 20170619, Digital file 2_1-7, 5 emails)
    1) Chelsea: West 23rd Street storefronts (Chelsea Box Depot and Rising Dragon Tattoos); 2,3) Chelsea: interior of barber shop and customers through front wondow; 4) View from behind backstop of Central Park Ballfield 5 of two baseball players with skyline in background; 5, 6) Edward Koch Queensboro Bridge/59th Street Bridge, from PS1 in Queens; 7) Upper West Side: Northeast corner of Columbus Avenue at 69th Street.
  - Chinatown (11 photos), 2011 June 12 (Digital folder 20130613, Digital file 1_01-11)
    Photos take on or around Eldridge Street, including Cheng Sheng Import and Export (Eldridge and Grand), Prosperity Dumpling storefront, Mahjong tiles/dice.
  - Times Square billboards (1 photo + 1 email), 2012 February (Digital folder 20170621, Digital file 3_1, email)
  - Freedom Tower under construction (3 photos + 3 emails), 2013 April (Digital folder 20170620, Digital file 1_1-3, 3 emails)
    Views from the top of Rockefeller Center, the Westside Highway, and detail of tower's top.
  - Floral Park, Queens (1 photo + 1 email), 2013 April (Digital folder 20170620, Digital file 2_1, email)
    Bird's-eye view from penthouse apartment in North Shore Towers.
  - New York Public Library, Rose Reading Room (1 photo + 1 email), 2013 April (Digital folder 20170620, Digital folder 3_1, email)
  - Manhattan Bridge (9 photos + 1 email), 2013 April (Digital folder 20170620, Digital file 4_1-9, email)
    Details of bridge taken from car on the bridge.
  - Manhattan skyline, south from roof garden of Metropolitan Museum of Art (1 photo + 1 email), 2014 May (Digital folder 20170621, Digital file 2_1, email)
  - Manhattan's East Side / Roosevelt Island / Tram (9 photos + 7 emails), 2014 August 20 (Digital folder 20170704, Digital file 1_1-9, 7 emails)
    Views from the Roosevelt Island tram of the Edward Koch Queensboro Bridge/59th Street Bridge, East River, and 1st Avenue traffic; views of Midtown Manhattan skyline from Roosevelt Island; and view of Long Island City with Pepsi Cola sign.
  - Central Park and area (3 photos + 3 emails), 2014 August (Digital folder 20170705, Digital file 2_1-3, 3 emails)
    1) Entrance to Ethical Culture School on Central Park West; 2) ceiling of the underpass at Bethesda Fountain; 3) Central Park South skyline from the Park.
  - 9/11 Memorial (9 photos + 1 email), 2014 August (Digital folder 20170706, Digital file 1_1-9, email)
  - Night Hotel, Times Square (3 photos + 1 email), 2014 December 14 (Digital folder 20141214, Digital file 1_1-3, email)
    Images of contrasting old and new hotel signage.
  - 125th Street, looking north (14 photos + 2 emails), 2015 April 2 (Digital folder 20150402, Digital file 1_01-14, 2 emails)
    These images are focused on the ironwork of the elevated train trestles.
  - Upper Manhattan. Broadway from 137th Street to about 163rd Street (82 photos + 2 emails), 2015 June? (Digital folder 20150612, Digital file 1_01-82, 2 emails)
    Includes storefronts, shop displays, pedestrians.
  - Central Park, summer (4 photos + 1 email), 2015 June? (Digital folder 20150613, Digital file 1_1-4, email)
  - 125th Street (40 photos + 1 email), 2015 June? (Digital folder 20150619, Digital file 1_01-40, email)
    Includes storefronts, signage, store displays, building facades, graffiti on steel grates, pedestrians.
  - Greenwich Village (27 photos + 1 email), 2015 June 25 (Digital folder 20150625, Digital file 1_01-27, email)
  - Riverside Park, the Boat Basin and Pier i Café (34 photos + 1 email), 2015 July (Digital folder 20150702, Digital file 1_01-34, email)
  - Bowery Mission (6 photos + 1 email), 2015 July 4 (Digital folder 20150704, Digital file 1_1-6, email)
  - Upper West Side. West 68th Street between Central Park West & Columbus Avenue (16 photos + 1 email), 2015 July 10 (Digital folder 20150711, Digital file 1_01-16, email)
  - Upper West Side. Central Park West & West 68th Street (3 photos + 1 email), 2015 July 11 (Digital folder 20150711, Digital file 2_1-3, email)
    Images of First Church of Christ Scientist front entrance.
  - Views from the High Bridge (15 photos + 1 email), 2015 July 14 (Digital folder 20150714, Digital file 1_01-15, email)
  - Hans Hofmann mosaic mural, High School of Graphic Communication Arts, exterior, 49th Street (14 photos + 1 email), 2015 July (Digital folder 20150721, Digital file 2_01-14, email)
  - Hans Hofmann mosaic mural, 711 Third Avenue, lobby (11 photos + 1 email), 2015 July (Digital folder 20150721, Digital file 3_01-11, email)
  - Lee Krasner/Ronald Stein mosaic mural, 2 Broadway, exterior (9 photos + 1 email), 2015 July 24 (Digital folder 20150724, Digital file 1_1-9, email)
  - Morgan Library, interior, Sunday brunch (15 photos + 1 email), 2015 July 27 (Digital folder 20150727, Digital file 1_01-15, email)
  - Upper West Side, The Belnord (1 photo + 1 email), 2015 July (Digital folder 20150728, Digital file 1_1, email)
    On north side of 79th Street between Broadway and Amsterdam Avenue.
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, front plaza and fountain (8 photos + 1 email), 2015 July 28 (Digital folder 20150728, Digital file 2_1-8, email)
  - Brooklyn Public Library area (40 photos + 3 emails), 2015 July 31 (Digital folder 20150731, Digital file 1_01-40, 3 emails)
    Eastern Parkway (17 photos), Grand Army Plaza fountain (9) and Grand Army Plaza arch (14).
  - Midtown. Esposito's Pork Shop storefront (1 photo + 1 email), 2015 July (Digital folder 20170123, Digital file 1_1, email)
    38th Street at 9th Avenue.
  - 125th & 126th streets. (4 photos +2 emails), 2015 August 6 (Digital folder 20150806, Digital file 1_1-4, 2 emails)
    2 images of buildings on 126th between Adam Clayton Powell and Malcolm X boulevards; 2 images of a building on the north side of 125th Street near Adam Clayton Powell Boulevard.
  - Upper West Side, West 73rd Street (2 photos + 1 email), 2015 August (Digital folder 20150807, Digital file 1_1-2, email)
    2 images of detail of the gate on the 73rd Street side of the Apple Savings Bank (formerly the Central Savings Bank).
  - Upper West Side (12 photos + 1 email), 2015 August (Digital folder 20150807, Digital file 2_01-12, email)
    The Ansonia (on Broadway at 73rd Street), some houses on West 68th Street, and corner of Columbus Avenue (east side) and 74th Street.
  - Washington Square Park (43 photos + 1 email), 2015 August 3 (Digital folder 20150807, Digital file 3_01-43, email)
  - Upper West Side (3 photos + 1 email), 2015 August (Digital folder 20150810, Digital file 1_1-3, email)
    The Dorilton (171 West 71st Street) and other buildings on the south side of 71st between Amsterdam and Columbus avenues.
  - Upper West Side (2 photos + 1 email), 2015 August (Digital folder 20150810, Digital file 2_1-2, email)
    East side of Columbus Avenue between 71st and 72nd streets, and the northeast corner at 72nd Street.
  - Chelsea (5 photos + 1 email), 2015 August (Digital folder 20150810, Digital file 3_1-5, email)
    22nd Street between 9th and 10th avenues (brownstones).
  - Upper West Side (9 photos + 1 email), 2015 August (Digital folder 20150814, Digital file 2_1-9, email)
    The San Remo towers shot from 74th Street at Columbus Avenue; Columbus (west side) between 74th and 75th streets; and the north side of 74th between Columbus and Amsterdam.
  - Upper West Side (2 photos + 2 emails), 2015 August (Digital folder 20170709, Digital file 1_1-2, 2 emails)
    1) Dorchester on Broadway between West 68th and 69th streets; 2) buildings at corner of Broadway and West 69th Street.
  - 7th Avenue (7 photos + 1 email), 2015 August 19 (Digital folder 20150819, Digital file 1_1-7, email)
    5 images of the interior and exterior of the Peter McManus Cafe (bar), including proprietor John McManus, on northwest side of 19th Street and 7th Avenue. Also, east side of 7th Avenue at 18th Street and a south view of 7th Avenue from 18th Street.
  - 6th Avenue at 18th and 19th streets (12 photos + 5 emails), 2015 August 21 (Digital folder 20150821, Digital file 1_01-12, 5 emails)
    Primarily views of 6th Avenue looking north and south from 18th and 19th streets. Also similar perspectives on 7th Avenue.
  - On the Manhattan Bridge (78 photos + 2 emails), 2015 August 24 (Digital folder 20150824, Digital file 1_01-78, 2 emails)
    Vviews from the south pedestrian walkway of the Manhattan Bridge and details of features of the bridge, including graffiti. Images begin on the Brooklyn side and end in Chinatown on the Manhattan side.
  - Upper West Side (6 photos + 2 emails), 2015 September 18 (Digital folder 20150920, Digital file 1_1-6, 2 emails)
    Images of details on buildings on West 71st Street between Central Park West and Columbus Avenue.
  - On the Williamsburg Bridge (64 photos + 1 email), 2015 September 29 (Digital folder 20150930, Digital file 1_01-64, email)
    Images from a walk starting at Peter Luger's in Williamsburg, Brooklyn, and crossing the bridge into Manhattan. A few street level views on either side of the bridge, views from the bridge, and primarily details of the bridge and walkway, including graffiti, steel framework, MTA train and tracks, etc.
  - Upper West Side. 90th St and West End Avenue (3 photos + 1 email), 2015 October 11 (Digital folder 20151012, Digital file 1_1-3, email)
  - Central Park. Autumn (20 photos + 1 email), 2015 October (Digital folder 20151022, Digital file 1_01-20, email)
  - Central Park. Autumn (14 photos + 1 email), 2015 October 27 (Digital folder 20151027, Digital file 1_01-14, email)
  - Upper West Side. Halloween decorations (12 photos + 1 email), 2015 October 27 (Digital folder 20151027, Digital file 2_01-12, email)
    Decorated homes on West 69th Street between Columbus Avenue and Central Park West.
  - SoHo. Cleveland & Kenmare streets, Corner Deli (1 photo + 1 email), 2015 October (Digital folder 20170823, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Flatiron District (6 photos + 1 email), 2015 November 3 (Digital folder 20151103, Digital file 1_1-6, email)
  - City views from the terraces of the Whitney Museum (7 photos + 1 email), 2015 November (Digital folder 20151104, Digital file 1_1-7, email)
  - Upper West Side (10 photos + 1 email), 2015 November 5 (Digital folder 20151105, Digital file 1_01-10, email)
    North side of West 67th Street between Columbus Avenue and Central Park West, including front of 67th Street Studios, Central Park Studios, and other buildings.
  - Central Park. Autumn (46 photos + 1 email), 2015 November 5 (Digital folder 20151105, Digital file 2_01-46, email)
    These photos emphasize the park's fall foliage colors.
  - Central Park. Autumn (47 photos + 1 email), 2015 November 8 (Digital folder 20151108, Digital file 1_01-47, email)
    Most of these photos emphasize the park's fall foliage colors.
  - Midtown. 8th Avenue between 39th and 40th streets (4 photos + 1 email), 2015 November 9 (Digital folder 20151111, Digital file 1_1-4, email)
  - Upper West Side, West 69th Street, holiday wreaths (6 photos + 1 email), 2015 December 6 (Digital folder 20151206, Digital file 1_1-6, email)
  - Upper West Side (1 photo + 1 email), 2015 December 7 (Digital folder 20151208, Digital file 1_1, email)
    West side of Columbus Avenue, between 68th and 69th streets.
  - Upper West Side. The Ansonia (2 photos + 1 email), 2015 December 1 (Digital folder 20151211, Digital file 1_1-2, email)
  - Greenwich Village (3 photos + 1 email), 2015 December 12 (Digital folder 20151216, Digital file 1_1-3, email)
    South west corner of Christopher and Bleecker streets.
  - East Village (1 photo + 1 email), 2015 December 13 (Digital folder 20151216, Digital file 2_1, email)
    South side of 11th Street looking west, just west of 1st Avenue.
  - Upper East Side / Central Park (1 photo + 1 email), 2015 December 13 (Digital folder 20151216, Digital file 3_1, email)
    Northeast corner of 66th Street and 5th Avenue looking west into Central Park.
  - Upper West Side (1 photo + 1 email), 2015 December 16 (Digital folder 20151218, Digital file 1_1, email)
    Northwest corner of 76th and Broadway, including part of the Hotel Belleclaire.
  - Upper West Side. The Eldorado (1 photo + 1 email), 2015 December 19 (Digital folder 20151219, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Greenpoint, Brooklyn (15 photos + 2 emails), 2015 December 21 (Digital folder 20151222, Digital file 1_01-15, 2 emails)
    Mostly views of Manhattan Avenue, north and south sides around Greenpoint Avenue, Kent Avenue and Java Street.
  - Upper West Side (11 photos + 1 email), 2015 December 25 (Digital folder 20151227, Digital file 1_01-11, email)
    West side of Columbus Avenue from 69th to 79th streets.
  - Greenwich Village. Bleecker Street storefronts (2 photos + 1 email), 2015 December (Digital folder 20170822, Digital file 1_1-2, email)
    O. Ottomanelli & Sons meat market and Rocco's pasticceria
  - Central Park, snow covered (35 photos + 1 email), 2016 February 5 (Digital folder 20160206, Digital file 1_01-35, email)
  - Central Park West, horse and buggy (1 photo + 1 email), 2016 January (Digital folder 20160216, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Greenwich Village (10 photos +1 email), 2016 January (Digital folder 20160216, Digital file 2_01-10, email)
    Most of the photos are of storefronts and rowhouses, with one view looking south to the Freedom Tower.
  - Dyker Heights, Brooklyn (3 photos + 1 email), 2016 January (Digital folder 20160216, Digital file 3_1-3, email)
    13th Avenue at 79th Street.
  - Various (3 photos + 1 email), 2016 February (Digital folder 20160216, Digital file 4_1-3, email)
    1) Upper West Side: Amsterdam Avenue looking south from the west side of the street at 69th Street. 2) Midtown: 5th Avenue looking southwest at 51st Street. 3)Yellow taxi and horse and buggy on Central Park South.
  - Upper West Side (2 photos + 1 email), 2016 March? (Digital folder 20160303, Digital file 1_1-2, email)
    Belnord Apartments on the north side of West 86th Street between Broadway and Amsterdam Avenue, and northeast corner of Amsterdam and 86th.
  - Central Park. Conservatory Garden, in winter snow (25 photos + 1 email), 2016 March 4 (Digital folder 20160304, Digital file 1_01-25, email)
  - High-rise buildings on Broadway at 66th Street (2 photos + 1 email), 2016 March 6 (Digital folder 20160307, Digital file 1_1-2, email)
  - Lower Manhattan, Fulton Street, barber shop storefront (1 photo + 1 email), 2016 March (Digital folder 20160311, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Greenwich Village (18 photos + 3 emails), 2016 March 13 (Digital folder 20160314, Digital file 1_01-18, 3 emails)
    10th Street between Bleecker Street and West 4th Street, and Bleecker and Perry streets.
  - World Trade Center Transportation Hub (51 photos + 2 emails), 2016 March (Digital folder 20160316, Digital file 1_01-51, 2 emails)
    Primarily includes exterior and interior views of the Santiago Calatrava-designed Oculus, with other interior views and exteriors of surrounding buildings, including the Freedom Tower.
  - SoHo (1 photo + 1 email), 2016 March 16 (Digital folder 20160316, Digital file 2_1, email)
    West side of the Bowery, looking south from Prince Street.
  - Upper West Side. 190 West 90th Street (1 photo + 1 email), 2016 March 18 (Digital folder 20160319, Digital file 1_1, email)
  - Brooklyn Heights (3 photos + 2 emails), 2016 March 25 (Digital folder 20160327, Digital file 1_1-3, 2 emails)
    Corner of Willow and Clark streets, and 36 Clark.
  - Park Slope, Brooklyn. 8th Avenue (13 photos + 1 email), 2016 March 31 (Digital folder 20160401, Digital file 1_01-13, email)
  - Upper Manhattan (3 photos + 1 email), 2016 April 6 (Digital folder 20160406, Digital file 1_1-3, email)
    Murals on buildings on Broadway between 156th and 157th streets.
  - East Village (2 photos + 1 email), 2016 April? (Digital folder 20160415, Digital file 1_1-2, email)
    Two brick buildings on 4th Street between Lafayette and the Bowery.
  - Upper West Side. 72nd Street subway station building (1 photo + 1 email), 2016 April 19 (Digital folder 20160426, Digital file 2_1, email)
  - Upper West Side. Corner of 71st Street and Columbus Avenue (1 photo + 1 email), 2016 May (Digital folder 20160506, Digital file 1_1, email)